<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gate of the Reach, Fear Under The Mountain!</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gate of the Reach, Fear Under The Mountain!</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:11:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Narrinesh the Monk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/narrinesh-the-monk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:11:36 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/narrinesh-the-monk/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the year 1400, Narrinesh the Dragonborn Rogueish Monk of the Astral Self and sworn vegetarian, was one of the four heroes of legend to foil the Necromancer&amp;rsquo;s plans in the Gate of the Reach fortress under the mountain.&#xA;Click here to visit the main page!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luth Amastacia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/luth-amastacia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:11:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/luth-amastacia/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the year 1400, Luth Amastacia, a Half-Elf Pact of the Blade Warlock bound to a flaming Aspect of Corellon, was one of the four heroes of legend to foil the Necromancer&amp;rsquo;s plans in the Gate of the Reach fortress under the mountain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stuu the Dwarf</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/stuu-the-dwarf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:11:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/stuu-the-dwarf/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In year 1400 DR, Stuu the Dwarf, a cook of the highest order who others called an Oath of Ancients Paladin, was one of the four heroes of legend to foil the Necromancer&amp;rsquo;s plans in the Gate of the Reach fortress under the mountain. A loyal ally and frightening enemy, Stuu traveled the land over with a good hat on his head and a firm stout in his belly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nirvana Knives</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/nirvana-knives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:10:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/nirvana-knives/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In year 1400 DR, Nirvana Knives, a Tiefling Soul Knife Rogue, was one of the four heroes of legend that foiled the Necromancer&amp;rsquo;s plans in the Gate of the Reach fortress under the mountain. At once a self-determined rogue and calculating leader, Nirvana would stop at nothing to achieve her own desires, believing the ends always justify the means. She relentlessly pursued this path, at times, against the wishes of her own friends and companions to see her greater vision achieved.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
